Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
Then, thus, a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Come above the king.
We're on Earth, a legendary!
If you can show your breath,
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted.
Ain't no beginners.
Cause if you want it,
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise,
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day.
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece.
I'll be the first.
I'll put it be so bad.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on the wheel.
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting.
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go.
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end.
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day, I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed?
I'm done playing through,
it's a wave in the air.
The world I'm feeling
alive, look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go.
We go.
All right, here I go.
This is it.
This is my new home.
He isn't spewing blood everywhere,
so I guess he's better now.
I don't get it. This sucks.
I want to swim, too. You can.
All we have to do is get you a bubble.
Oh, really? Uh-huh.
We can have one made in the city.
Sound good? Yeah!
This is a lucky break.
Sanji's blood type is
rare, and we're all out.
What?
That sounds like seriously bad news.
Hey, Kuma? Huh?
Well, I'm here.
There's somebody I'd really like
to see if we can find them somehow.
Oh? Don't tell me.
The Mermaid Princess?
Nope.
It's Jinbei.
They call him Boss down here.
Wait, when you say Jinbei, you're
talking about the Warlord Jinbei?
Or, I mean, former Warlord, since he
resigned after the whole war thing.
Yeah, he's a good friend of mine.
Huh?
Him and the Pirate Empress?
You make some weird friends
when we're not around.
When Ace died two years ago, I had
a tough time pulling it together.
In fact, I doubt I'd even be here
right now if it wasn't for his help.
Can't wait to talk to him again!
See you on Fishman Island in two years!
Be sure to bring your entire crew along.
I look forward to meeting everyone.
He said to meet here, and there's
no way I'm going to let him down.
Now that you mention it,
I heard he went to
Marineford with you when you
rang that bell and
everyone got all worked up.
You know where we can find him?
Well, it's kind of tricky,
because Boss doesn't exactly live
on the island with everyone else.
Since he resigned from the warlords,
they have to treat him
like a normal pirate again.
That means all the fishman pirates
can't stay in the city anymore,
so they found a new place to live.
It's not too far from here,
but that's where you'll have
to go if you want to see him.
What?
That sounds like a pain.
This place has some dumb rules.
I know it seems weird, but even
though we're all the way down here,
the war of the best ended
up affecting us, too.
Kuma! Kuma! Kuma! Kuma! Kuma!
There's a big ship coming!
It's a ship from the palace.
Yeah, but maybe nobody's on it.
Don't be stupid.
Of course someone is.
So did you see somebody
on the ship or not?
No, not yet.
But it was for sure the royal family ship.
They don't usually come around here.
Maybe they've come here to arrest Luffy
because he didn't enter
the city the right way.
So what if they do?
You guys had better hide
before they get here.
She's right.
That ship's the Royal Gondola.
I thought so. I knew.
Maybe. Totally. So what?
Even so, I doubt anyone from the
Royal Family is actually riding on it.
This corner of the island's
sort of out of the way for them,
so they don't usually bother.
Attention, all citizens!
The three Neptune brothers have arrived.
Greetings, ladies of the cove!
I hope that you can
answer an inquiry of mine.
The princess,
no
hide
here
and stay still.
Hey, water?
I received a report that someone
entered the city illegally.
Have they come by here, perhaps?
If they have, and you've seen them, be
sure to tell me if us all are teeter!
Mambo, mambo, shiki shiki
moonfish, why we gotta do this?
Let's party with the ladies!
I'm sorry, but we
haven't seen anyone here.
They sound like common thugs.
Are they really that important?
Surely they don't demand the
attention of princes such as you.
Perhaps.
We have yet to ascertain their identities,
so it may be too early to say just yet.
He doesn't know! Let's hear it!
Nobody! Knock him up! Nobody!
What's all this commotion? Huh?
Oh, man, it's the princess
from Neptune's army!
What are they doing here?
What a pain in the ass. Now what?
I see.
Well, I thank you all.
We shall search elsewhere.
Forgive me for interrupting your leisure.
We'll dance again sometime.
And away we go. Latina. Bye-bye.
Perhaps the border guards
were just seeing things.
What is that?
What did I do?
That was too much blood.
He needs help now.
He's done poor.
All that pent-up lust
let loose in one shot!
Wait, no mistaking it.
That's the pirate's Straw Hat Luffy.
Ammo Knights, go! Yes, sir!
Well, look at that.
How convenient.
I don't know, the gods
are gonna catch him first.
Our orders are clear, but we don't want
to start crap with the Neptune army.
Wait, hold on a second, please.
We don't want to fight, we
can sort out our crimes later!
But right now there's an emergency.
Our friend has lost a lot of
blood and we need a donor, quick!
If you leave him here or throw him in
jail, he'll be dead within an hour!
His blood type is SRH negative.
I know it's rare, but does
someone here have it? Anyone?
Fishmen and humans do have the
same kind of blood, don't they?
Chopper, Jim We don't have time!
Guys, this is serious!
Sanchi, we are not losing you over this!
Please, I'm begging you!
Whatever it takes!
I can't let my friend die!
Chopper Chin, I'm sorry.
Fishmen and humans do have the same kind
of blood, but the situation is complicated.
The thing is...
Hamo, hamo, hamo, hamo, hamo.
Get a load of these humans.
You really are stupid, aren't you?
Weren't you a big enough
jerk the last time we met?
His name is Hammond, sir.
He's from the Fishmen District.
Hammo, Hammo, Hammo.
You're not getting a damn drop
from anybody on this island.
Why would we share our blood with
disgusting creatures like you?
Humans aren't worth a thing down here.
And even if someone did help you,
decent fishmen like us who hate humans
would make sure they were punished for it.
He can bleed out right
here for all I care!
Many fishmen would happily watch him die.
There's a law for this.
You know when we followed for a long time,
fishmen are forbidden to
share blood with humans.
No matter what.
Law sucks!
Don't blame me for it.
After all, it was humans who
set the rule in the first place.
Our blood may be the same, but for
ages you've treated us like monsters.
Or worse, like? animals.
Your blood was too good for us.
In fact, that's why
Fisher Tiger, the hero of
this island, died.
He fought to free slaves of all races,
and when that battle took
its toll on his body,
when he lied bloody and battered, not
a single human would offer their blood
to return his kindness.
A transfusion would have saved
him, but because of humans, he
died.
Well, it's not much of a choice, really.
Your friend is going to
die, and you're coming
to the Fishman District with me.
Heart Jones, the captain of
the new Fishman Pirates, is
expecting you, and he doesn't
like to wait. That's enough!
Hey, who cares about some
stupid rule in the first place?
You don't have to listen to this, thug.
There's someone's life
on the line here.
We'll do anything it takes to repay you.
Now is not the time to get stuck On pride
Jamie come along Straw Hat.
I'll take you by force if I have to
Charles
I'm not joining your stupid group.
I already told you
My word, he made quick work of them.
It just gave up!
I guess Luffy can tame sea monsters now?
What happened?
That was crazy!
Impressive.
Luffy-chan, up here!
Bring Sanji-chan up here!
We'll go back to town!
There's lots of humans there, so we
might be able to find a blood donor.
Let's hurry. I'm coming.
Cool. Ready to go.
Thanks, Kuma. Sure.
We need to head over
to town. Is that okay?
Yes.
It's not fair.
I'd do anything in the
world to save his life,
but I don't have the right blood type.
No,
it's nothing for you to
feel bad about if he wasn't
such a perv this would have
happened in the first place!
Look at her.
He's dying, and he's
still thinking about boobs
We may be friends,
but considering the way you and
Hachi got treated back on Sabo
Odi I should have guessed
something like this would happen.
There's some deep-rooted
stuff going on here
Yeah, and to be honest, I
don't know how this will go.
There's no promise anyone
will help us back in town.
We're counting on human donors for blood,
but I haven't seen any
at all this past month.
In fact, your ship is the first
one we've had in a long time.
Why?
I thought everyone had
to come through here.
Yeah, it wasn't like this before.
Nobody can say for certain,
but we think someone's attacking the
travelers, like what happened with you guys.
There's something going
on in this kingdom,
and I have a sinking feeling
it's about to get ugly.
Please, ladies, you must be forthright.
Why did you try to conceal
those pirates from us?
We're sorry, Prince.
They aren't bad people.
It sounds like what
happened wasn't their fault.
They're Kami's friends, and they
got split up from their crew,
so we didn't want them to be thrown
in jail as soon as they got here.
I hope they find a donor for Sanji.
Alas, you misunderstood us.
Their method of entry is no concern.
They're quite famous.
It would only be a small formality.
We don't consider them enemies, after all.
Yeah!
We had different business with them!
Re mi fa sol a ti!
Then this is all our fault.
We had a message to pass
on to them, from Jinbei.
Hey, Sanji!
Are you awake? Talk to us!
Where am I?
You pulled through!
We're safe in a town right
by the harbor. I'm scared.
You almost lost all
the blood in your body.
I was starting to think
we'd never find you a donor.
That was a real close call.
That so? Wow.
What in the hell happened
to me you shouldn't
be sitting up so quickly
you need to rest i
just don't get it i
mean the fish could have
given blood but no instead
we had to run all over
town looking for another
human which took forever
i know right i was
starting to lose hope there
i'm sorry i appreciate
what you did though but
i just don't remember
much why'd this happen?
Where was I, and what was I doing?
When I think about it,
it's all a big blub.
No, let go of me!
If you try to force the memories,
you could relapse. Oh, yeah.
I almost forgot, Sanji.
You haven't met your donors.
So here, say hi.
And also, thank you.
Wait, could my savior
have been a dainty girl?
Don't worry.
We're only human.
After all, if we don't look
out for each other, who will?
Don't worry, babe.
If you want, we can give you more.
Looks like he's back to his old self.
It's not exactly gratitude.
Luffy, can I see the cut on
your arm for a second please?
It's positive.
Thought so.
Luffy, that wound's
poisonous. Oh, wow. Really?
That must have been the
sting I felt earlier.
One of the fishmen got me.
You don't seem poisoned. You feeling okay?
Yeah.
Either way, we should be careful.
This stuff's probably deadly.
You sure you're all right?
Yep.
Wow.
So weird.
It sounds crazy.
But you must have somehow developed an
antibody to fight against this kind of stuff.
Tell me, have you ever experienced
a poisoning like this in the past?
Let's see.
Yeah, back when I was at Impel
Down, I almost got killed that way.
That is not funny at all.
Yeah, it is.
I bet it was that octopus swordsman.
I mean, he blocked my punch, so
he's got to be strong. No prob.
Next time I'll be ready
they're
so
loud I think that came from by that cove
don't care I've got bigger problems these
guys are messed up real bad and what's
worse.
Straw Hat got poisoned too.
I'm dead if he dies.
I'm positive I heard their screams come
from here.
Ishii!
Where are you?
This is where I saw them last.
But where in the world could they
have gone?
Did anyone else hear them say
something about opening up a barrel?
She's the owner of
this place.
She okayed Sanji resting here.
Be Madam Charlie.
Cool, thanks and stuff.
Has the blonde boy's
condition improved at all?
Yep, but it's best he doesn't
meet you because you're so
beautiful, right?
That would be bad.
Also, we probably shouldn't
tell him he's in the back
of the mermaid cafe.
Not if we want him to get well.
Why keep it a secret?
Because doctor's orders.
Chakra's pretty sure that if Sanjee-chin
finds out he's gonna have a bad relapse.
What a
strange prognosis.
Hey, big lady! Fish lady!
Wow, that was rude. Come on.
Tell me what this is.
It's
beautiful.
It's also not on the list of
things you're allowed to touch.
Oh, that?
You're looking at Madam
Charlie's crystal ball.
With it, she can see the future.
Her precognitive visions
are Why she's famous well it
used to be not anymore the
future isn't ours to know right?
Sounds rough oh by the way
how do mermaids take a dump?
we are not talking
about mermaid poop again
Sorry why don't you take
the rest of the day off?
Kuma i think your friends would appreciate
a tour Of the island really you sure?
it's fine you deserve it
seeing as you're always
working so Hard besides business
has been slow with human
guests so uncommon these days
so we have to be Extra good
hosts the girls from the
cove should show up soon then
we'll have more hands around
Here than a starfish more
than starfish oh that's right
crap i should have already
delivered papa Goose clams
by now wow i have no idea
what's going on i bet he's
getting mad waiting for his food
Not quite he's enjoying the cafe an old
friend of his suddenly came into town and
they've been Living it up since he arrived
wait he's here i
didn't want to bring
this up in front of her But madam told me
a lot of stories from when she was little
she said in those days human Pirates came
to the island all the time but that was
quite a while ago about a year before
the great Pirate era began it's hard for
her to talk about things sometimes especially
when she foresees bad Stuff like the
war at marineford and whitebeard's death
what can you imagine knowing something
Horrible will happen that you can't stop
that must be terrifying
hey where's chopper?
oh he said he Who's going to hang
out here and look after Sunch?
Come on, you two.
Hurry up. Okay.
Right now, we're on what's
considered Coral Hill's main street.
And that is the primary
entrance to the Mermaid Cafe.
Man, I thought I was
going to starve to death.
They might only serve snacks.
No, you're good.
We've got cakes and sea
fruit, too. And meat?
Uh, no.
We merfolk don't really eat meat and fish.
But we have wakame Barrel,
mosugu tarts, kelp souffle.
You call that food?
Wait, we do have some meat.
From shellfish.
Scallop sandwiches, plant pizza, and...
Don't give me the bad name!
Stop talking!
Whoa, okay, be cool.
Let's just go inside.
Yeah, let's all go find papagoo.
Shellfish!
What the hell kind of crab is that?
Thank you very much! Yeah!
Oh, wow, it's Brooke! Hooray!
Huh?
Luffy and Usopp?
And Kuma, you've become
such a lovely young lady.
Hey, guys!
You had no idea how much I've missed you!
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
Hey, Papagu!
Sorry it's been so long!
I guess that makes you Papagu's
old friend we heard about!
Come see us again, k?
I had a great time, Soul King.
I'll be back, lovely ladies.
Lots of bones to go around.
I've gone limp.
No, I haven't.
Skeletons are always rigid.
Good thing I'm already dead, or I would
probably die of embarrassment right now.
This cafe's really put
Brooke in rare form.
Yeah, whatever's going on inside
must be held up there, boss.
Huh?
What are you in such a hurry for?
I know you're interested in the cafe,
and I get that, but it's not
like it's going anywhere.
Let's come back when you
have your whole crew.
Bone Daddy and I were just
about to head back to my place.
Why don't you guys come with us?
If you do, you can eat all
the Sea King meat you want.
Did you say meat?
Yeah, I did.
I'm a wild animal. You feel me?
It's not like I eat boring shellfish.
I need food with a little more bite.
Oh, by the way, I brought
your order of clams. Sweet!
My favorite treat is finally here!
Oh, so much for your diet!
Look, merfolk are the only
ones who don't eat meat.
Fishmen eat the stuff all the time, so
it's not like you can't get it here.
It's just not as common.
Yes! That's great!
Oh, Vander Decken thought so.
But why is there a wanted
poster for a ghost?
Yeah, wasn't this guy on
the haunted ship we saw?
You saw him? For real?
Uh-huh. No way. Whoa.
Our nation's been looking
for him for years now.
The dude's a pirate and
a Newgate undersea thief.
I'll tell you all about it on the trip.
Let's load up. And go!
Story goes, Vandertekin was hard up.
The guy was totally head over heels for
the mermaid princess of the Ryugu kingdom.
He was so desperate, he
sent love letters daily.
How stalkery, you know?
Gave up letters, started sending gifts
instead, then threats, so to marry her!
It's a fucking puppy!
Feels great!
It's bringing him up!
Are you even listening to me? Sure!
Sorry about that.
The mermaid princess got
scared, and so of course.
The stalker became a national concern.
Yeah, but that was just the beginning.
Her father, King Neptune, got mad.
Which led to him sending the three princes
you saw earlier off to hunt Vander Decken.
But even with the army,
they can't find him.
Oh, come on, Kuma.
You stole all my thunder.
By the way, King Neptune's
the god of the sea.
Plus, he's in control of this country.
If that's not enough responsibility,
he has four children to take care of.
The mermaid princess is the youngest.
So obviously the three princes are
the older kids in the royal family.
Please, I got this.
Great, but something
still doesn't make sense.
Vander Decken must be quite ancient.
If he isn't a ghost, I imagine
he's a few hundred years old.
At least.
Huh.
You're right, that doesn't make sense.
That is, unless you ignore the rumors.
Now, there's no denying that he existed.
But the truth of the matter is
that the legendary sea captain
Vander Decken died sometime after
he arrived here on Fishman Island?
and hasn't been heard from since.
That said, the ship you say you saw
probably was the Flying Dutchman, but...
It's his descendant who's on board.
He's...
He's Vander Decken the Ninth.
Wow, that's a lot!
Well, I have to say, it's a relief to
find out he's not a ghost after all.
Believing we had come into
contact with someone from
the afterlife was making me
contemplate my own mortality.
And considering I'm a skeleton,
I don't have much of that left.
I just wanted to tell an exciting story.
Man, I thought merfolk and
fishmen all look the same,
but the more I see, the less they do.
Check out those old ones down there.
Their fins are split like Granny Kokoro.
See those babies? Right there.
You'll notice the father is a fishman, but
the children are a mix of both species.
That's because when a
mermaid and a fishman
love each other very much
and decide to get busy,
Their kids can come out
looking like either parent.
Bam!
Four possibilities for the happy family.
Whoa, that's why they all look different.
So cool.
All right, we finally
made it to the highway.
Whoa!
This is fast!
What's up with that place?
Oh, nothing.
It's a candy factory.
Really?
Then why is there a pirate flag on it?
Oh, that?
That flag's everywhere here.
By the entrance and the
harbor, it's a big deal.
And for good reason at that, it
symbolizes that we're protected. You see,
the flag belongs to a famous pirate
named Charlotte Lin-Lin of the New World.
But she's better known as Big
Mom, one of the four emperors.
Whoa, that's no joke.
Back before the war in Marineford,
Whitebeard was this island's guardian.
But now that he's dead, someone
else had to take his place.
And that someone happened to be her.
Okay.
The thing is, she demands a whole ton
of candy in exchange for her services.
Hence the factory that you just saw.
That's weird.
This country wouldn't be
able to survive without
the protection of
powerful people like her.
After all, this is a dangerous
place where pirates come and go,
and more often than not,
they aren't very friendly.
Yeah, I guess.
Plus, she's filling in
where Whitebeard left off,
so that's gotta mean she's
a good person, doesn't it?
Depends on how you look at it.
Whitebeard never asked for anything
in return for his protection.
Big Mom, on the other hand, treats it
like a business rather than a charity.
Still, that's cool.
An emperor. Like shakes. Crazy.
Hope they get to meet her.
Eyes forward.
This is where all the
celebrity types live.
Fishburly Hills.
That tall building right in front is
Papa Goose's house, where we're going.
All that?
For one starfish?
Ah!
We have to do something.
We can't let this happen.
That's Madame Shirley, from the cafe.
What's the matter?
Please, please tell us.
What's wrong?
Why are you upset?
Something must be done.
Now before it's too late.
Sure.
What do we do?
Find him!
The pirate boy in a Straw Hat!
It's an emergency!
He must leave the country! Now!
There's no time!
Wait, you're having a premonition?
I swore I wouldn't use this power, but
something about that boy felt off to me.
I...
I had no choice but to
look into the future.
What's going to happen?
Tell us, what did you see?
We have to know!
Charlie, tell us!
Madam, please!
I hope I'm wrong, and
that it won't happen.
I saw him clearly,
surrounded by flames,
because Straw Hat Luffy, Fishman Island,
our country will be destroyed.